No,
رقم،
Brother,
أخ،
Did you see this knife?
هل رأيت هذا السكين؟
You're abusing the dog here.
أنت تسيء معاملة الكلب هنا.
I'm not blind.
أنا لست أعمى.
There's a way to heaven. If you don't go,
هناك طريق إلى الجنة.  إذا لم تذهب ،
There's no way out of hell. You're here to vote.
لا يوجد مخرج من الجحيم.  أنت هنا للتصويت.
It's been a long time since you were upset.
لقد مضى وقت طويل منذ أن كنت مستاء.
Don't come near me.
لا تقترب مني.
If you come any closer, I'll kill her.
إذا اقتربت أكثر ، سأقتلها.
I'm not going there.
لن أذهب هناك.
Don't touch her.
لا تلمسها.
Of course,
بالطبع،
we are gangsters.
نحن رجال عصابات.
It's also ethical.
إنها أيضًا أخلاقية.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
You … You don't talk about martial arts?
أنت ... لا تتحدث عن فنون الدفاع عن النفس؟
My Lord.
ربي.
Take Her Ladyship back.
استرجع سيادتها.
The rest of you,
بقية لكم،
take them away.
خذهم بعيدا.
His Lordship is wise.
سيادته حكيمة.
You're still here.
أنت ما زلت هنا.
My Lord,
ربي،
I found it.
لقد وجدتها.
Bai Qinglang ordered it.
أمر باي تشينغلانغ ذلك.
Bai Qinglang,
باي تشينغلانغ ،
fake imperial edict,
مرسوم إمبراطوري مزيف ،
He doesn't have the guts.
ليس لديه الشجاعة.
Keep investigating.
استمر في التحقيق.
Yes.
نعم.
His Lordship and
سيادته و
Bai Qinglang are going back to the capital.
سيعود باي تشينغلانغ إلى العاصمة.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Your Ladyship
سيدتك
I want to see His Lordship go back
أريد أن أرى سيادته تعود
and look good. This is the dark place.
وتبدو جيدة.  هذا هو المكان المظلم.
What can you see?
ماذا ترى؟
I didn't look at him.
لم أنظر إليه.
Who on earth
من على وجه الأرض
are those people?
هم هؤلاء الناس
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I just want His Lordship's life.
أنا فقط أريد حياة سيادته.
By the way, Your Ladyship,
بالمناسبة يا سيدتك ،
His Lordship didn't want to lock you up,
سيادته لا تريد أن تحبسك ،
It's just that it's not peaceful outside these two days,
كل ما في الأمر أن الوضع ليس سلميًا خارج هذين اليومين ،
don't you know?
الا تعلم
In order to catch them,
من أجل القبض عليهم ،
His Lordship hasn't slept for two days.
سيادته لم تنم لمدة يومين.
Don't go out these two days.
لا تخرج في هذين اليومين.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I'll eat you.
سوف أكلك.
Su Qiu,
سو تشيو ،
go and look for it later.
اذهب وابحث عنه لاحقًا.
What did those people say about Duke Jingbei?
ماذا قال هؤلاء الناس عن دوق جينغبى؟
Yes, Miss.
نعم آنستي.
You've found the right person.
لقد وجدت الشخص المناسب.
Just wait and see.
فقط انتظر وانظر.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
this mutton is a tribute from the north.
هذا الضأن هو تكريم من الشمال.
When I was seven or eight months old,
عندما كان عمري سبعة أو ثمانية أشهر ،
I was the most tender.
كنت الأكثر رقة.
Seven or eight months.
سبعة أو ثمانية أشهر.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
about the fake imperial edict,
حول المرسوم الإمبراطوري المزيف ،
The mutton is too tender.
لحم الضأن رقيق جدا.
It's too early to kill him now.
من السابق لأوانه قتله الآن.
My Lord, it's obviously
ربي ، من الواضح
disaster relief food from Hexi,
أغذية الإغاثة في حالات الكوارث من Hexi ،
You must say it's your birthday gift.
يجب أن تقول إنها هدية عيد ميلادك.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
His Lordship has his own reasons
سيادته لها أسبابه الخاصة
for this arrangement.
لهذا الترتيب.
And the flood in Longxi.
والفيضان في Longxi.
Zhi,
زي ،
Brother,
أخ،
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Here's the thing.
هنا الحاجة.
My brother-in-law doesn't want you to be bored.
أخي في القانون لا يريدك أن تشعر بالملل.
He asked me to come and see you.
طلب مني أن آتي لأراك.
You seem to be living a good life.
يبدو أنك تعيش حياة جيدة.
Zhi.
زهي.
Are you listening to me?
هل تستمع لي؟
Let's eat.
لنأكل.
The dishes are getting cold.
الأطباق تزداد برودة.
< Jingbei Marquis Black Material
<جينغبى ماركيز مادة سوداء
Collection >, why are you still reading this stuff?
مجموعة> ، لماذا ما زلت تقرأ هذه الأشياء؟
Did Su Qiu give it to you?
هل أعطاها لك Su Qiu؟
Give me all of them.
أعطني كل منهم.
Brother,
أخ،
and this.
وهذا.
That's too much.
هذا كثير جدا.
He has no conscience.
ليس لديه ضمير.
It's really hard for me
من الصعب حقًا بالنسبة لي
to explain this to you.
لشرح هذا لك.
But you have to know,
لكن عليك أن تعرف ،
what's on it,
ماذا يوجد عليها
That's because there's something fishy about it
هذا بسبب وجود شيء مريب فيه
and it's totally uncountable to deliberately erase it,
ومن غير المعقول محوه عمدًا ،
Brother,
أخ،
let's make it clear for him.
دعونا نوضح الأمر له.
Dear,
عزيزي،
would you like some tea?
هل تريد بعض الشاي؟
Look,
نظرة،
there's no poison.
لا يوجد سم.
Are you hungry?
هل انت جوعان؟
Do you want to eat something delicious?
هل تريد أن تأكل شيئًا لذيذًا؟
I know I was wrong.
أعلم إنني كنت مخطئ.
Got it.
فهمتك.
What did you do wrong?
ماذا فعلت غلطا؟
I shouldn't have.
لا يجب أن أمتلك.
I shouldn't suspect you of eating human flesh.
لا يجب أن أشك في أنك تأكل اللحم البشري.
I shouldn't have let the bad guys go.
لا ينبغي أن أترك الأشرار يذهبون.
You shouldn't eat human flesh.
لا يجب أن تأكل اللحم البشري.
Sorry,
آسف،
I won't do it again.
لن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
There will be another time.
سيكون هناك وقت آخر.
No, no next time.
لا ، ليس في المرة القادمة.
It won't happen again.
لن يحدث ذلك مرة أخرى.
Come and sleep.
تعال ونم.
A little girl like you,
فتاة صغيرة مثلك
who's so sweet and soft,
من هو لطيف جدا و ناعم ،
I'll take one bite at a time,
سآخذ قضمة واحدة في كل مرة ،